<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:weightSum="1">



    <ImageView
        android:layout_width="fill_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:id="@+id/news_curr_pic"
        android:src="@drawable/pic"
        android:layout_columnSpan="3"
        android:layout_row="1"
        android:layout_gravity="center_horizontal"
        android:layout_margin="3dp" />

    <TextView
        android:layout_width="fill_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:textAppearance="?android:attr/textAppearanceLarge"
        android:text="Large Text"
        android:id="@+id/news_curr_title"
        android:layout_gravity="center_vertical"
        android:layout_weight="23.25"
        android:layout_below="@+id/news_curr_pic"
        android:layout_alignLeft="@+id/news_curr_pic"
        android:layout_alignStart="@+id/news_curr_pic"
        android:layout_margin="3dp" />

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/news_curr_date"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_gravity="left"

        android:paddingTop="2dp"
        android:text="11:23 25.11.2015"
        android:textColor="#343434"
        android:textSize="15sp"
        android:layout_below="@+id/news_curr_title"
        android:layout_alignRight="@+id/news_curr_pic"
        android:layout_alignEnd="@+id/news_curr_pic" />


    <ScrollView xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
        android:id="@+id/scroll"
        android:layout_width="fill_parent"
        android:layout_height="fill_parent"

        android:layout_below="@+id/news_curr_date"
        android:layout_alignLeft="@+id/news_curr_title"
        android:layout_alignStart="@+id/news_curr_title">


        <TextView
            android:layout_width="fill_parent"
            android:layout_height="fill_parent"
            android:textAppearance="?android:attr/textAppearanceSmall"
            android:text="Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. Текст новости для проверки скрола. "
            android:id="@+id/news_curr_text"
            android:layout_alignParentBottom="true" />

    </ScrollView>




</RelativeLayout>
